Tufts-New England Medical Center Records MS224
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Planning office records, 1932 -- 1985; 1960 -- 1975; MS224.005; 31.2 Linear Feet
  - Master plan files, 1954 -- 1972; MS224.005.003
    - Master plan - surveys - patient/visitor - volunteer instructions, MS224.005.039.00062 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - surveys - program and space needs, 1962; MS224.005.039.00063 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - surveys - population, student, MS224.005.039.00064 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - surveys - South Cove proposals, 1961; MS224.005.039.00065 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - surveys - Tufts Dental School development and execution, 1962; MS224.005.039.00066 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - surveys - T-NEMC parking lots, 1961; MS224.005.039.00067 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - tax portrait, 1962; MS224.005.039.00068 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - US government HHFA programs, MS224.005.039.00069 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - surveys - patient/visitor - pedestrian circulation, MS224.005.039.00070 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - utilities, electric, MS224.005.039.00071 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - T-NEMC - proposed land areas, 1965; MS224.005.039.00072; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 39)
    - Master plan - transportation, MS224.005.039.00073 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - surveys - patient/visitor 2nd, MS224.005.039.00074 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - surveys - pedestrian circulation - publicity, 1962; MS224.005.039.00075 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - surveys - pedestrian circulation - survey stations, MS224.005.039.00076 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - patient/visitor survey development materials, 1962; MS224.005.039.00077 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - patient/visitor development and execution survey, 1962; MS224.005.039.00078 (Box 39)
    - Master plan - surveys - patient/visitor draft copies, MS224.005.039.00079 (Box 40)
    - Master plan - surveys - patient/visitor 1st, MS224.005.040.00001 (Box 40)
    - Master plan - nursing housing surveys, 1966; MS224.005.040.00002 (Box 40)
    - Master plan - survey - patient/visitor, 1962; MS224.005.040.00003 (Box 40)
    - Master plan - survey - medical students, MS224.005.040.00004 (Box 40)
    - Office - annual report of director, 1963; MS224.005.040.00005 (Box 40)
    - Office - architects, organization, MS224.005.040.00006 (Box 40)
    - Office - architecture 6202, 1962; MS224.005.040.00007 (Box 40)
    - Office - architecture 6201, 1962; MS224.005.040.00008 (Box 40)
    - Planning office - design service, 1962 -- 1963; MS224.005.040.00009 (Box 40)
    - Master plan - functions - psychiatry, MS224.005.040.00010 (Box 40)
    - Master plan - survey - Boston Floating tabulation, MS224.005.040.00011 (Box 40)
    - Master plan - survey - Dental School (T-NEMC), 1962 -- 1963; MS224.005.040.00012 (Box 40)
    - Master plan - T-NEMC model display plans, 1967; MS224.005.040.00013 (Box 40)
    - Master plan - surveys - Boston Floating Hospital physical facilities copies of questionnaires, 1962; MS224.005.040.00014 (Box 40)
    - Master plan - surveys - BFH physical facilities, 1962; MS224.005.040.00015 (Box 40)
    - Office - architecture 6205, MS224.005.040.00016 (Box 40)
    - Quincy Housing - general, 1970 -- 1972; MS224.005.040.00017 (Box 40)
    - Quincy Housing - TAC contract, 1970; MS224.005.040.00018 (Box 40)
    - Office - architecture 6204, 1962; MS224.005.040.00019 (Box 40)
    - Office - architecture 6203, 1962; MS224.005.040.00020 (Box 40)
    - Master plan - surveys (visual) T-NEMC photographs, MS224.005.040.00021 (Box 40)
    - A Feasability Study of Married Student Housing at T-NEMC, 1965-1975, MS224.005.040.00022; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 40)
  - Budget reports, 1968 -- 1973; MS224.005.004
    - Monthly report - bureau of census art 5 - general conditions, 1969; MS224.005.040.00023 (Box 40)
    - T-NEMC chart of accounts, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.005.040.00024 (Box 40)
    - Expense codes for construction and renovation, 1970; MS224.005.040.00025 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - director of facilities, 84600, 1970 -- 1972; MS224.005.040.00026 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - parking - structure, 84703-84103, 1970; MS224.005.040.00027 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - educational building systems, 1970; MS224.005.040.00028 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - medical library, 1969; MS224.005.040.00029 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - NEMCH new building, 1970; MS224.005.040.00030 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - materials handling - supply, 84105, 1970; MS224.005.040.00031 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - central stores, 84104, 1970; MS224.005.040.00032 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - Tufts central health, 1970; MS224.005.040.00033 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - commercial development, 1970; MS224.005.040.00034 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - dental health science building, 1970; MS224.005.040.00035 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - NEMCH new building, PHA, 1970; MS224.005.040.00036 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - married student housing, 1970; MS224.005.040.00037 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - dental tower, 1969; MS224.005.040.00038 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - Basic Health Science Building, 1970; MS224.005.040.00039 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - Utility Supply Center, 1970; MS224.005.040.00040 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - borings, 1970; MS224.005.040.00041 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - central utility plant, 1970; MS224.005.040.00042 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - communications, 1970; MS224.005.040.00043 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - contingency, 1970; MS224.005.040.00044 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - elevators, 1970; MS224.005.040.00045 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - master planning, 1970; MS224.005.040.00046 (Box 40)
    - Budget report - NEMCH radiation therapy, 1970; MS224.005.040.00047 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - files, foundation and excavation, 1970; MS224.005.040.00048 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - superstructure I-A, 1970; MS224.005.040.00049 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - surveys, 1970; MS224.005.040.00050 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - utilities, 1970; MS224.005.040.00051 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - vibration consultant, 1970; MS224.005.040.00052 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - office administration, 1970; MS224.005.040.00053 (Box 40)
    - Budget reports - recreational facilities, 1970; MS224.005.040.00054 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence - approvals for special students, 1970 -- 1972; MS224.005.040.00055 (Box 40)
    - Department budget report, 1970; MS224.005.040.00056 (Box 40)
    - USC charges, 84420, 1973; MS224.005.041.00001 (Box 41)
    - T-NEMC - housing Quincy school - budget control, 1971; MS224.005.041.00002 (Box 41)
    - Budget reports - food consultant, 1970; MS224.005.041.00003 (Box 41)
    - T-NEMC report on financial statements, 1970; MS224.005.041.00004 (Box 41)
    - Charges to 44117, 1968; MS224.005.041.00005 (Box 41)
    - Quincy Housing - budget control, MS224.005.041.00006 (Box 41)
    - T-NEMC charges to garage, 1973; MS224.005.041.00007 (Box 41)
    - T-NEMC/NEMCH TAC comparison, 1969; MS224.005.041.00008 (Box 41)
    - Budget reports - general initiative and parking, 1970; MS224.005.041.00009 (Box 41)
    - T-NEMC parking garage - sprague, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.005.041.00010 (Box 41)
    - Personnel resumes, 1969; MS224.005.041.00011 (Box 41)
  - Unit files, 1937 -- 1969; MS224.005.005
    - Units - Dental School - notes, 1963; MS224.005.041.00012 (Box 41)
    - Units - Dental School - questionnaire, 1967; MS224.005.041.00013 (Box 41)
    - Units - Dental School - planning seminar, MS224.005.041.00014 (Box 41)
    - Units - Dental School - standards for dental offices, MS224.005.041.00015 (Box 41)
    - Units - Dental School - statistics, 1961 -- 1967; MS224.005.041.00016 (Box 41)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - administration, 1937; MS224.005.041.00017 (Box 41)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - budget, 1961; MS224.005.041.00018 (Box 41)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - design conference, 1962; MS224.005.041.00019 (Box 41)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - "Floating Hospital Administration", 1962; MS224.005.041.00020; New England Journal of Medicine (Box 41)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - design and construction proposal, 1963; MS224.005.041.00021 (Box 41)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - design grant, 1962; MS224.005.041.00022 (Box 41)
    - Units - Bingham Associates Fund, 1961; MS224.005.041.00023 (Box 41)
    - Units - Boston Dispensary Admission Forms, MS224.005.041.00024 (Box 41)
    - Units - Boston Dispensary - elderly housing, 1961; MS224.005.041.00025 (Box 41)
    - Units - Boston Dispensary - housing, 1961; MS224.005.041.00026 (Box 41)
    - Units - Dental Clinic survey notebook, 1963; MS224.005.041.00027 (Box 41)
    - Units - Boston Dispensary, MS224.005.041.00028 (Box 41)
    - Units - Boston Dispensary - pediatrics, MS224.005.041.00029 (Box 41)
    - Units - Boston Dispensary - psychiatric design, 1962; MS224.005.041.00030 (Box 41)
    - Units - Boston Dispensary - statistics, 1961 -- 1963; MS224.005.041.00031 (Box 41)
    - Units - Dental School - Biodental Engineering, 1963 -- 1965; MS224.005.041.00032 (Box 41)
    - Units - Dental School clinics, 1963; MS224.005.041.00033 (Box 41)
    - Units - Dental School - curriculum study, 1963; MS224.005.041.00034 (Box 41)
    - Units - Dental School - Dental Center, 1962; MS224.005.041.00035 (Box 41)
    - Units - Dental School - Dental Center grant, 1962; MS224.005.041.00036 (Box 41)
    - Units - Dental School - interfraternity, 1962; MS224.005.041.00037 (Box 41)
    - Units - Dental - office survey, MS224.005.041.00038 (Box 41)
    - Units - NECH dietary department, 1963; MS224.005.041.00039 (Box 41)
    - Units - PC/NECH - Farnsworth OR, Central Supply Annual Report, 1962; MS224.005.041.00040 (Box 41)
    - Executive T-NEMC financial statements, 1964 -- 1966; MS224.005.041.00041 (Box 41)
    - Executive T-NEMC - general, MS224.005.041.00042 (Box 41)
    - Executive - Trustees and members of T-NEMC corporation, MS224.005.041.00043 (Box 41)
    - Extended Care - geriatric housing, 1968; MS224.005.041.00044 (Box 41)
    - Functional - parking, 1966; MS224.005.041.00045 (Box 41)
    - T-NEMC parking, 1965 -- 1967; MS224.005.041.00046 (Box 41)
    - Executive - Executive director, Wolf, George Jr., 1961; MS224.005.041.00047 (Box 41)
    - Executive - general Philip Hallen notes, MS224.005.041.00048 (Box 41)
    - Executive - TNEMC annual meeting, 1964 -- 1965; MS224.005.041.00049 (Box 41)
    - Executive - permanent charity fund, 1961; MS224.005.041.00050 (Box 41)
    - Executive - public relations - Mrs. Mazza, 1966; MS224.005.041.00051 (Box 41)
    - Executive - common services - cooperative laundry, 1960; MS224.005.041.00052 (Box 41)
    - Executive - development, 1962; MS224.005.041.00053 (Box 41)
    - Executive - common services - director's report, 1963; MS224.005.041.00054 (Box 41)
    - Departments - BD home medical service, interiors, 1962; MS224.005.041.00055 (Box 41)
    - Departments - BD home medical service, objectives, 1961; MS224.005.041.00056 (Box 41)
    - Departments - clinical research unit, PC/NECH, 1961; MS224.005.041.00057 (Box 41)
    - Departments - common services - organization, MS224.005.041.00058 (Box 41)
    - Departments - Common services - personnel, 1966; MS224.005.041.00059 (Box 41)
    - Departments - dietary - coffee shop interiors, 1962; MS224.005.041.00060 (Box 41)
    - Departments - flow diagrams, 1960; MS224.005.041.00061 (Box 41)
    - Departments - geriatric facilities, 1963; MS224.005.041.00062 (Box 41)
    - Departments - planning office graphic standards, MS224.005.041.00063 (Box 41)
    - Departments - planning office interiors, 1962; MS224.005.041.00064 (Box 41)
    - Departments - planning office - reports, 1963; MS224.005.041.00065 (Box 41)
    - Departments - planning office - summer program, 1963; MS224.005.041.00066 (Box 41)
    - Departments - public affairs - Bennet sign, 1961 -- 1962; MS224.005.041.00067 (Box 41)
    - Departments - public relations, 1965 -- 1967; MS224.005.041.00068 (Box 41)
    - Departments - radiology, PC/NECH, MS224.005.041.00069 (Box 41)
    - Departments - X-ray, PC/NECH, 1962; MS224.005.041.00070 (Box 41)
    - Units - PC/NECH statistics, 1961 -- 1964; MS224.005.041.00071 (Box 41)
    - Units - PC/NECH trustees, 1961; MS224.005.041.00072 (Box 41)
    - Units - PC/NECH general, 1959 -- 1963; MS224.005.041.00073 (Box 41)
    - Units - PC/NECH X-ray department, 1963; MS224.005.041.00074 (Box 41)
    - Units - TNEMC ambulatory care, 1967; MS224.005.041.00075 (Box 41)
    - Units - Medical and Dental schools federal aid, 1962; MS224.005.041.00076 (Box 41)
    - Units - Medical and Dental schools charter, 1951; MS224.005.041.00077 (Box 41)
    - Units - Medical and Dental schools library, 1963; MS224.005.041.00078 (Box 41)
    - Units - TNEMC maps, 1957; MS224.005.041.00079 (Box 41)
    - Units - Tufts University trustees, 1961; MS224.005.041.00080 (Box 41)
    - Units - TNEMC objectives committee, 1962; MS224.005.041.00081 (Box 41)
    - Units - TNEMC news releases, 1964 -- 1965; MS224.005.041.00082 (Box 41)
    - Units - architects - TNEMC, 1964 -- 1968; MS224.005.041.00083 (Box 41)
    - Units - Ziskind building cost scquisition and construction, MS224.005.041.00084 (Box 41)
    - Units - NECH interview with Mr. Spiker, 1962; MS224.005.041.00085 (Box 41)
    - Units - PC/NECH parking lot, planting box, sign, 1962; MS224.005.041.00086 (Box 41)
    - Units - NECH position descriptions, MS224.005.041.00087 (Box 41)
    - Units - PC/NECh research projects, 1956; MS224.005.041.00088 (Box 41)
    - Units - Medical school basic science and clinical departments, 1963; MS224.005.041.00089 (Box 41)
    - Units - Medical school Dean Maloney, 1966; MS224.005.041.00090 (Box 41)
    - Units - Medical school department of preventive medicine, 1962; MS224.005.041.00091 (Box 41)
    - Units - Medical school department of preventive medicine, Columbia Point Health Center, 1962 -- 1965; MS224.005.041.00092 (Box 41)
    - Units - Medical school students, 1960 -- 1961; MS224.005.041.00093 (Box 41)
    - Units - NECH administrative report, 1965; MS224.005.041.00094 (Box 41)
    - Units - NECH admission forms, 1961; MS224.005.041.00095 (Box 41)
    - Units - PC/NECH architects, MS224.005.041.00096 (Box 41)
    - Units - NECH - dietary department job descriptions, 1962; MS224.005.042.00001 (Box 42)
    - Units - PC/NECH executive director, 1961 -- 1962; MS224.005.042.00002 (Box 42)
    - Units - TNEMC land building space inventory drafts, 1962; MS224.005.042.00003 (Box 42)
    - TNEMC preliminary projection and existing conditions, MS224.005.042.00004 (Box 42)
    - Practical CPM for Construction, 1968; MS224.005.042.00005; Priluck, Herbert M.; Hourihan, Peter M. (Box 42)
    - T-NEMC Health Information Committee, 1966 -- 1969; MS224.005.042.00006 (Box 42)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - design grant, MS224.005.042.00007 (Box 42)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - grant HM00235-01-C5, 1962; MS224.005.042.00008 (Box 42)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - design grant, 1962; MS224.005.042.00009 (Box 42)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - design grant, MS224.005.042.00010 (Box 42)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - design grant - publicity, 1962; MS224.005.042.00011 (Box 42)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - design grant - study, 1962; MS224.005.042.00012 (Box 42)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - executive trustees, 1961; MS224.005.042.00013 (Box 42)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - general, MS224.005.042.00014 (Box 42)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - intensive care, 1966; MS224.005.042.00015 (Box 42)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - program impressionistic sketch, 1964; MS224.005.042.00016 (Box 42)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - pediatric hospitals, 1961; MS224.005.042.00017 (Box 42)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - research grant application, 1964 -- 1965; MS224.005.042.00018 (Box 42)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - research report 2, 1963; MS224.005.042.00019 (Box 42)
    - Units - Floating Hospital - study group, 1963; MS224.005.042.00020 (Box 42)
    - Notes from a tour of medical facilities in the Midwest, 1963; MS224.005.042.00021 (Box 42)
    - T-NEMC - land building space inventory, 1962; MS224.005.042.00022 (Box 42)
    - Study of Existing Facilities and New Possibilities for the Boston Dispensary, 1962; MS224.005.042.00023 (Box 42)
    - Space alllocations and projections, 1963; MS224.005.042.00024 (Box 42)
    - Other medical center facilities, 1963; MS224.005.042.00025 (Box 42)
  - Office files, 1950 -- 1969; MS224.005.006
    - Office - work programs, MS224.005.042.00026 (Box 42)
    - Standards - community, Rothman file, 1950; MS224.005.042.00027 (Box 42)
    - Office - time sheets, 1960 -- 1964; MS224.005.042.00028 (Box 42)
    - Office - staff, MS224.005.042.00029 (Box 42)
    - Office - staff recommendations, 1962; MS224.005.042.00030 (Box 42)
    - Office - programming, 1957; MS224.005.042.00031 (Box 42)
    - Office - service contracts, 1964; MS224.005.042.00032 (Box 42)
    - Radiology remodeling, Pratt 2, 1966 -- 1967; MS224.005.042.00033 (Box 42)
    - Office - associated staff research, MS224.005.042.00034 (Box 42)
    - Office - budget, 1961; MS224.005.042.00035 (Box 42)
    - Office - budget foundations, 1961; MS224.005.042.00036 (Box 42)
    - Office - community, Rothman file, 1964; MS224.005.042.00037 (Box 42)
    - Office - conference AMA - AIA, 1965; MS224.005.042.00038 (Box 42)
    - Office - furniture costs, 1962; MS224.005.042.00039 (Box 42)
    - Office - graphics blueprinters, 1961; MS224.005.042.00040 (Box 42)
    - Office - graphics NEMC hospital study, 1966; MS224.005.042.00041 (Box 42)
    - Office - materials, fabrics, design-tex, 1962; MS224.005.042.00042 (Box 42)
    - Office - NECH sign cost estimate, 1962; MS224.005.042.00043 (Box 42)
    - Office - construction, 1962; MS224.005.042.00044 (Box 42)
    - Office - organization, 1969; MS224.005.042.00045 (Box 42)
    - NECH personnel supervisory study group, 1968; MS224.005.042.00046 (Box 42)
    - Office - file organization, MS224.005.042.00047 (Box 42)
  - James Eacker files, 1961 -- 1980; MS224.005.007
    - Andover conference, 1969; MS224.005.042.00048 (Box 42)
    - T-NEMC Andover Planning conference, 1969; MS224.005.042.00049 (Box 42)
    - Planning Office bills, invoices, late charges, 1970 -- 1972; MS224.005.042.00050 (Box 42)
    - Planning Office - NEMCH C and E orders, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.042.00051 (Box 42)
    - Planning - long range planning, 1970; MS224.005.042.00052 (Box 42)
    - Pediatric study, 1970; MS224.005.042.00053 (Box 42)
    - Quincy School married student housing, MS224.005.042.00054 (Box 42)
    - Master plan, 1973; MS224.005.042.00055 (Box 42)
    - Administrative meeting, 1969; MS224.005.042.00056 (Box 42)
    - St. James Church, 1969 -- 1971; MS224.005.042.00057 (Box 42)
    - Master planning, 1970 -- 1973; MS224.005.042.00058 (Box 42)
    - BRA - contract H, 1972; MS224.005.042.00059 (Box 42)
    - T-NEMC planning committee, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.005.042.00060 (Box 42)
    - T-NEMC office project rwequest forms, 1970 -- 1973; MS224.005.042.00061 (Box 42)
    - Reports and proposals, 1968 -- 1970; MS224.005.042.00062 (Box 42)
    - Staffing - planning office, 1969 -- 1972; MS224.005.042.00063 (Box 42)
    - South Cove - parcel C-1, 1972; MS224.005.042.00064 (Box 42)
    - South Cove - parcel C-2, 1972; MS224.005.042.00065 (Box 42)
    - BRA utility meetings, South Cove project R-92, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.043.00001 (Box 43)
    - T-NEMC budget, 1970; MS224.005.043.00002 (Box 43)
    - Funding - T-NEMC gifts, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.043.00003 (Box 43)
    - South Cove Subway Coordinating Committee, 1969 -- 1970; MS224.005.043.00004 (Box 43)
    - Subway tunnel sewer line - Fuller building lot, 1969; MS224.005.043.00005 (Box 43)
    - South Cove Project: Shea Road, 1970 -- 1972; MS224.005.043.00006 (Box 43)
    - South Cove Project: BRA correspondence, 1968 -- 1973; MS224.005.043.00007 (Box 43)
    - South Cove - utilities, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.005.043.00008 (Box 43)
    - Boston area construction program, 1972; MS224.005.043.00009 (Box 43)
    - Harvard Business Review, 1971; MS224.005.043.00010 (Box 43)
    - Affirmative action reports, 1972; MS224.005.043.00011 (Box 43)
    - Tufts EEO, 1970; MS224.005.043.00012 (Box 43)
    - T-NEMC budget, 1972 -- 1973; MS224.005.043.00013 (Box 43)
    - T-NEMC budget, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.005.043.00014 (Box 43)
    - T-NEMC budget, 1973; MS224.005.043.00015 (Box 43)
    - T-NEMC budget, 1970 -- 1972; MS224.005.043.00016 (Box 43)
    - Sprague - parking garage, 1971 -- 1973; MS224.005.043.00017 (Box 43)
    - T-NEMC- office relayout, 1971; MS224.005.043.00018 (Box 43)
    - T-NEMC TAC - special services account, 1971; MS224.005.043.00019 (Box 43)
    - T-NEMC - organization studies, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.005.043.00020 (Box 43)
    - T-NEMC - public health service hospital, 1972; MS224.005.043.00021 (Box 43)
    - Salary reviews, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.005.043.00022 (Box 43)
    - T-NEMC cost control, 1970 -- 1972; MS224.005.043.00023 (Box 43)
    - Harvard Business Review, 1971; MS224.005.043.00024 (Box 43)
    - Subcommittee on meetings handling, 1967 -- 1968; MS224.005.043.00025 (Box 43)
    - T-NEMC phase II spcifications, 1970; MS224.005.043.00026; T-NEMC Planning Office (Box 43)
    - San-Vel Concrete Corporation, MS224.005.043.00027 (Box 43)
    - T-NEMC Report, 1971; MS224.005.043.00028; T-NEMC (Box 43)
    - Barr and Barr, Inc. daily construction reports, 1970 -- 1972; MS224.005.043.00029 (Box 43)
    - Renovations, 1973; MS224.005.043.00030 (Box 43)
    - Summary and Excerpts from Doctors, Patients, and Health Insurance, 1961; MS224.005.043.00031; Somers, Herman Miles; Somers, Anne Ramsay (Box 43)
    - Saccoccio, Daniel, 1973; MS224.005.043.00032 (Box 43)
    - T-NEMC - properties, 1971 -- 1973; MS224.005.043.00033 (Box 43)
    - T-NEMC - budget, 1972 -- 1973; MS224.005.043.00034 (Box 43)
    - Parking garage - beef and ale wall contract, 1973; MS224.005.043.00035 (Box 43)
    - Budgets - parking garage, 1971 -- 1973; MS224.005.043.00036 (Box 43)
    - Parking garage - MBTA vent, 1973; MS224.005.043.00037 (Box 43)
    - T-NEMC facilities organization, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.005.043.00038 (Box 43)
    - Parking garage - rental space, 1972; MS224.005.043.00039 (Box 43)
    - Parking garage - Conrad reports, 1972; MS224.005.043.00040 (Box 43)
    - Elliot Paul Rothman, MS224.005.043.00041 (Box 43)
    - Parking garage - Sprague completion and final payment, 1972 -- 1973; MS224.005.043.00042 (Box 43)
    - Parking garage - inspection service, 1971; MS224.005.043.00043 (Box 43)
    - I-B financing, 1971; MS224.005.043.00044 (Box 43)
    - I-B cost consultants, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.005.043.00045 (Box 43)
    - I-B planning or programming, 1970 -- 1973; MS224.005.043.00046 (Box 43)
    - I-B agency approvals, 1971 -- 1972; MS224.005.043.00047 (Box 43)
    - Hospital I-B - F.P.P., 1970; MS224.005.043.00048 (Box 43)
    - Quincy School - housing T.A.C. contract, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.043.00049 (Box 43)
    - Quincy School - married student housing, 1971; MS224.005.044.00001 (Box 44)
    - Quincy School - committee minutes, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.044.00002 (Box 44)
    - T-NEMC Housing - cost consultant, 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.044.00003 (Box 44)
    - Quincy School - housing, active, 1971; MS224.005.044.00004 (Box 44)
    - Quincy School - married students housing, 1970; MS224.005.044.00005 (Box 44)
    - Quincy School - Boston Gas Co., 1970 -- 1971; MS224.005.044.00006 (Box 44)
    - Proposals from other medical schools' curriculums, 1964 -- 1967; MS224.005.044.00007 (Box 44)
    - Study carrel information, 1968; MS224.005.044.00008 (Box 44)
    - Support facilities, 1969; MS224.005.044.00009 (Box 44)
    - New Dimension in Urban Renewal, 1968; MS224.005.044.00010; The Architectural Forum (Box 44)